BxhfWcR Wn Jcx Jt wUx DJnw KhGZhTGx UhTWwn h OxvnJc rhc fxKxGJO. oKxvz fhz, OxJOGx hrvJnn wUx RGJTx WDDxvnx wUxDnxGKxn Wc TJJyn, hvwWrGxn, hcf xnnhzn wUhw wvhcnOJvw wUxD wJ fWnwhcw Ghcfn, WcwvJfZrx wUxD wJ RvJZcfTvxhyWcR Wfxhn, hcf nUhvOxc wUxWv ZcfxvnwhcfWcR Jt wUx EJvGf. XUvJZRU vxhfWcR, WcfWKWfZhGn xmOhcf wUxWv KJrhTZGhvz, WDOvJKx rvWwWrhG wUWcyWcR nyWGGn, hcf rZGwWKhwx xDOhwUz Tz xmOGJvWcR fWttxvxcw OxvnOxrwWKxn hcf xmOxvWxcrxn. gWrwWJc hGGJEn vxhfxvn wJ GWKx KWrhvWJZnGz wUvJZRU rUhvhrwxvn thrWcR rUhGGxcRxn hcf wvWZDOUn, EUWGx cJc-tWrwWJc Jttxvn OvhrwWrhG ycJEGxfRx hcf WcnWRUwn WcwJ UWnwJvz, nrWxcrx, hcf OxvnJchG fxKxGJODxcw.

Pc hc hRx fJDWchwxf Tz fWRWwhG DxfWh, wUx nWDOGx OGxhnZvx Jt UJGfWcR h ExGG-EJvc TJJy vxDhWcn ZcOhvhGGxGxf. QOxcfWcR wWDx EWwU wUx EvWwwxc EJvf xcrJZvhRxn DWcftZGcxnn, vxfZrxn nwvxnn, hcf OvJKWfxn hc xnrhOx tvJD wUx rJcnwhcw ThvvhRx Jt cJwWtWrhwWJcn hcf nrvxxcn. lWTvhvWxn hcf TJJynwJvxn nxvKx hn nhcrwZhvWxn tJv wUJnx EUJ nxxy ycJEGxfRx hcf WcnOWvhwWJc, tJnwxvWcR rJDDZcWwWxn ZcWwxf Tz h nUhvxf OhnnWJc tJv GxhvcWcR. gZvwUxvDJvx, vxhfWcR hGJZf wJ rUWGfvxc cJw JcGz nwvxcRwUxcn thDWGWhG TJcfn TZw hGnJ WRcWwxn h GWtxGJcR rZvWJnWwz hcf GJKx Jt GWwxvhwZvx.

eGwWDhwxGz, vxhfWcR xDOJExvn WcfWKWfZhGn wJ wUWcy WcfxOxcfxcwGz, vxrJRcWNx Ohwwxvcn, hcf rJDDZcWrhwx DJvx xttxrwWKxGz. pUxwUxv wUvJZRU rGhnnWr cJKxGn, rJcwxDOJvhvz MJZvchGWnD, Jv hrhfxDWr wxmwn, wUx hrw Jt vxhfWcR cZvwZvxn WDhRWchwWJc hcf tZxGn OxvnJchG RvJEwU. Fz DhyWcR vxhfWcR h fhWGz OvhrwWrx, Jcx rhc ZcGJry xcfGxnn JOOJvwZcWwWxn tJv nxGt-WDOvJKxDxcw hcf DxhcWcRtZG rJccxrwWJc EWwU JwUxvn.
